<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome To Meow Town 🐱</title>
    <link>https://meowsus.github.io</link>
    <atom:link href="https://meowsus.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:28:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/04/05/Saturday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I did. I did tell myself I wouldn’t work this weekend. Then again, if I consider personal projects as “work,” I’ll probably never get to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project is more of a product, to be honest. It’s a goal of mine to diversify my revenue streams (I say while feeling slightly nauseated). As David could tell you, I spent about seven months unexpectedly without income, a...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/04/05/Saturday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/04/02/Wednesday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;As I sit down to write, I pour myself about 3 ounces of Mijenta Tequila Blanco to wash the taste of Trader Joe’s Crunchy Chili Onion Peanuts out of my mouth. The flavor combination is an abomination as well as an act of penance for my lack of writing as of late. My apologies, David.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week I’ve been uninspired. The project I’ve been working on just wrapped up age...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/04/02/Wednesday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/03/19/Wednesday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;As I’ve already mentioned &lt;a href=&quot;/2025/02/28/Friday.html&quot;&gt;I’m skittish about being non-billable&lt;/a&gt;. Yet, here I am again, being paid to learn a thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m working on kiosk software, a niche my company seems eager to explore. I’m only about 7 weeks into working here but I think I’m settling in nicely. I’m able to apply a lot of the &lt;a href...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/03/19/Wednesday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/28/Friday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Admittedly my attitude toward being a contractor is a bit skewed. The guilt that I feel when I find myself reaching for my staff engineer hat is really unfounded. This has been reinforced many times over while speaking to my manager and his manager along with the other members of my team. I’m seen as a full time employee; the contract thing is just a formality. After being unemployed l...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/28/Friday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/23/Sunday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I touched a bit on this on &lt;a href=&quot;/2025/02/07/Friday.html&quot;&gt;the 7th&lt;/a&gt; but it was back in the forefront of my mind after a six-day work week. I did this to make sure I had 40 hours on my time sheet. One of the conditions for me accepting my current contract was that they were able to give me 40 hours of things to do per week. Would I die if I worked less? No. Ha...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/23/Sunday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/17/Monday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;After spending the last hour rejiggering the intent of this blog and adding an ASCII cat–for literally no reason–I think I’m ready to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&quot;/2025/02/11/Tuesday.html&quot;&gt;last post&lt;/a&gt; I hinted that there was a point to all my rambling. That point was that I’m busy. I’m a single dad. I have two kids. I own a home. I usually have a f...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/17/Monday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/11/Tuesday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Now that I fill my days with billable hours, I am becoming acutely aware of just how much time I wasted over the last six months. Moreover, I’m becoming acutely aware that &lt;em&gt;I work all the time&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take yesterday, for example. It was one of those Mondays when I didn’t have the kids in the morning. On these types of Mondays, I’ve told myself it’s best...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/11/Tuesday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/07/Friday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;It’s Friyay and I just worked my first honest-to-God 40-hour work week in probably three years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not saying that I’m one of those suspected corporate scofflaws who jag their days away while collecting maximal pay; the kind Silicon Valley is currently trying to drag back to the office five days a week to see if they need to be fired or not. I’m saying that, when s...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/07/Friday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/03/Monday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Sorry for the break, David, but I did end up going &lt;a href=&quot;/2025/01/25/Saturday.html&quot;&gt;a little crazy&lt;/a&gt;. I followed the whole self-scripting thing a bit too deeply, got frustrated, and took a two-week mental break. Well, kind of. I still made some pretty good progress on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/meowsus/journai&quot;&gt;Journai&lt;/a&gt;. Now I can wr...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/02/03/Monday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/25/Saturday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Ok, hi. I told myself I wouldn’t work this week after having the revelation that I am often guilty of rolling off one project and immediately onto another. I wanted to change that behavior and give myself a break for two weeks to try and process the experience of being unemployed for half a year while also trying to visualize and prepare for the path ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’ve ...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/25/Saturday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/21/Tuesday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;In lieu of journaling this morning, I wanted to write this post because my brain was all fired up after a series of information streams from yesterday connected in an interesting way for me this morning while I was staring at my dishes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday would have been &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/David_Lynch&quot;&gt;David Lynch&lt;/a&gt;’s 79th birthday...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/21/Tuesday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/19/Sunday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Long have I fantasized about having AI make my dinner for me. I came close tonight by asking ChatGPT to make a pasta sauce from the ingredients I had laying around the fridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be honest, this isn’t the first time I’ve queried Skynet for the answers to my dinner woes. In fact, when I worked at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.convictional.com/&quot;&gt;Convictional&lt...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/19/Sunday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/18/Saturday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Yes, it’s the weekend. No, I’m not really working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was reading &lt;a href=&quot;https://news.ycombinator.com&quot;&gt;Hacker News&lt;/a&gt; last night and saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://reedybear.bearblog.dev/ive-been-advocating-for-rss-support-and-you-should-too/&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt; advocating for more RSS feeds across the web. I’ve been an exclusive user ...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/18/Saturday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/17/Friday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;Welcome to this week’s installment of &lt;em&gt;Find-A-Job-Friday&lt;/em&gt;! Each Friday I spend an average of two hours sending resumes and cover letters out to an average of 5 companies, all while telling that little voice in the back of my brain that tries to convince me that it’s just an act of futility to &lt;em&gt;stfu&lt;/em&gt;, to use the parlance of digital times past.&lt;/p...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/17/Friday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/16/Thursday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I took the day off to clean today since I have some friends from Philadelphia staying with me over the weekend. I observed that my normal &lt;em&gt;omg I have to speed up my self-care routine&lt;/em&gt; feelings went totally out the window, and I was able to enjoy my journaling and exercise. I wrote a lot, actually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My morning journaling routine was really the impet...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/16/Thursday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/15/Wednesday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I got a late start today despite getting the kids to school on time. On a good drop-off day, I get back to my house around 8:30 in the morning, which leaves me a scant 30 minutes to journal, stretch, and meditate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, while journaling, I made an interesting observation: working for Ampwall is a distraction. When I was brought into the fold, it was at a time when ...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/15/Wednesday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday</title>
      <link>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/14/Tuesday.html
      </link>
      <description>
        &lt;p&gt;After a rocky morning with my newly christened tweenager, full of fights surrounding their ability to choose and apply clothing to their own damn bodies their own damn selves, I was finally out the door and off to their school only about 20 minutes after the bell rang. Every day is a gift.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I arrived home I had mere moments before my 9AM interview to refresh mys...
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>
        https://meowsus.github.io/2025/01/14/Tuesday.html
      </guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>